[{"question": " passport, check!  camera, check! traveller\u0092s cheques, check!", "answer": " who are you saying \"check\" too?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 5, "asentId": 6}, {"question": " myself. y\u0092know for remembering to pack a thing. yeah, you do a good thing, you get a check!  my mom does it, i never realized it was weird.", "answer": " yeah, my mom used to put her head in the oven. well, actually, she only did it the one time. but it was pretty weird.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 7, "asentId": 8}, {"question": "  hey!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 9, "asentId": 10}, {"question": " hey! are you ready yet?", "answer": " yep! you got the tickets?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 11, "asentId": 12}, {"question": " you got your passport?", "answer": " yeah, in my third drawer on my dresser. you don\u0092t want to lose that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 17, "asentId": 18}, {"question": " okay, if you need the vacuum, it\u0092s in my closet on the left-hand side. ah, the garbage bags are next to the refrigerator\u009a", "answer": " okay, okay, but rachel\u0092s gonna be here too, can\u0092t i just ask her this stuff?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 23, "asentId": 24}, {"question": " yeah, okay, give that a try!", "answer": "  all right! let\u0092s do it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 25, "asentId": 26}, {"question": " woo-hoo!!", "answer": " yeah, cheerie-o!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 27, "asentId": 28}, {"question": " london baby!", "answer": " okay, \u0091cause that\u0092s not gonna get annoying.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 29, "asentId": 30}, {"question": "  london baby!!", "answer": " hey, y\u0092know what? i was wrong.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 31, "asentId": 32}, {"question": " well, we\u0092re all here! i guess we should get going!", "answer": " ohhh, i wanna come over there and give you a hug and wish you luck on your wedding, but i don\u0092t\u0097can\u0092t get up.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 33, "asentId": 34}, {"question": " oh, i\u0092ll-i\u0092ll come hug you.", "answer": " great! yeah, could you bring me the newspaper?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 35, "asentId": 36}, {"question": " oh, have a great wedding!", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 39, "asentId": 40}, {"question": " oh, hey, chandler i wanna hug you too!", "answer": " hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 41, "asentId": 42}, {"question": " oh, and great! you might as well bring me my book, it\u0092s on the counter in your apartment.", "answer": " oh.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 43, "asentId": 44}, {"question": "  so, we\u0092re off.", "answer": " have fun!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 45, "asentId": 46}, {"question": " thanks!  ugh, i can\u0092t believe you\u0092re not gonna be there!", "answer": " oh, i know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 47, "asentId": 48}, {"question": " so-so come! why don\u0092t you come?", "answer": " what?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 49, "asentId": 50}, {"question": " to london! come to london. please? it\u0092ll mean so much to me.", "answer": " yeah, well, i gotta work, i\u0092m sorry.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 51, "asentId": 52}, {"question": " why-why can\u0092t you take a couple of days off?", "answer": " because, i can\u0092t! ross, i told you, no. i can\u0092t.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 53, "asentId": 54}, {"question": " this is my wedding.", "answer": " all right, y\u0092know what? we really are late! let\u0092s go! let\u0092s go! let\u0092s go!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 55, "asentId": 56}, {"question": " fine. you\u0092ll-you\u0092ll watch it on video when we get back.", "answer": "  here you go phoebe! here you go phobo! phewbedo! phaybobo.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 57, "asentId": 58}, {"question": "  thank you. (chandler kneels down with his arms spread waiting for his hug.", "answer": " thank you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 59, "asentId": 60}, {"question": " all right, let\u0092s go! bye, pheebs!", "answer": " bye, pheebs!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 61, "asentId": 62}, {"question": " come on! do something!", "answer": " i am, i\u0092m ignoring you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 67, "asentId": 68}, {"question": " oh, what the hell is that?", "answer": " it\u0092s london, baby! all right, the hotel\u0092s here.  wait. no, we wanna go\u009a no. i know.  i\u0092m gonna have to go into the map.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 71, "asentId": 72}, {"question": " okay, if you see a little version of me in there? kill it!", "answer": " i got it!  here we go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 73, "asentId": 74}, {"question": " okay. listen-listen, we\u0092re not gonna have to walk this way the entire time are we?", "answer": " shhh!  man, you made me lose it!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 75, "asentId": 76}, {"question": " \u009aand that was all before 10 o\u0092clock. the caterer rang and said it was going to be chicken kiev instead of chicken tarragon. and then the florist phoned to say there aren\u0092t any tulips. oh, and the chilliest has carpel-tunel syndrome. we\u0092re not gonna be\u009a", "answer": " whoa-whoa-whoa! emily,  honey, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 77, "asentId": 78}, {"question": " well, up yours too!", "answer": " what?! no! no! that\u0092s-that\u0092s time-out!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 79, "asentId": 80}, {"question": " sorry.", "answer": " sweetie, you gotta relax. everything\u0092s gonna be great, okay? come on. come on.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 81, "asentId": 82}, {"question": " chicken kiev?", "answer": " um-hmm! doesn\u0092t that sound delicious at the last minute?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 83, "asentId": 84}, {"question": " yeah, y\u0092know, but something like salmon which would be so much more elegant than the chicken. and, you wouldn\u0092t have to worry about the salmonella.  so, i can\u0092t wait to see this place you\u0092re getting married!", "answer": " yeah. yeah. yes, this place is beautiful. emily\u0092s parents got married here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 85, "asentId": 86}, {"question": " i still can\u0092t believe they\u0092re tearing it down. it really is the most lovely building you\u0092ll ever see. i mean it\u0092s over\u009a  oh my god!", "answer": " it\u0092s nice.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 87, "asentId": 88}, {"question": "  oh. oh my god. how can this be happening? what are we going to do?", "answer": " it\u0092s all right! everything\u0092s gonna be all right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 91, "asentId": 92}, {"question": " how\u0092s it gonna be all right?!", "answer": " uh-huh, i see that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 93, "asentId": 94}, {"question": "  okay, i talked to the guy with the shovel and i found out what happened.", "answer": " what? what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 95, "asentId": 96}, {"question": " all right! westminster abbey! hands down, best abbey i\u0092ve ever seen. hey!  okay. what do you think of the abbey, chandler?", "answer": " i think it\u0092s great. it\u0092s great. y\u0092know, they\u0092re thinking of changing the name of this place.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 99, "asentId": 100}, {"question": " really? to what?", "answer": " to put the camera away!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 101, "asentId": 102}, {"question": " oh. oh.", "answer": " oh, honey! don\u0092t get up! what do you need?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 105, "asentId": 106}, {"question": " oh, no. oh, nothing.", "answer": " come on! i am here to take care of you! what do you need? anything.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 107, "asentId": 108}, {"question": " okay, i have a wedgie.", "answer": " okay, that is all you.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 109, "asentId": 110}, {"question": " so-so, what do you want for lunch?", "answer": " oh, i don\u0092t know. i guess we have to eat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 111, "asentId": 112}, {"question": " yeah, i do. what\u0092s the matter?", "answer": " i\u0092m just bummed about the way i left things with ross. i shouldn\u0092t have lied to him about having to work. he seemed so mad at me.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 113, "asentId": 114}, {"question": " eh, don\u0092t be so hard on yourself. if someone i was still in love with was getting married\u009a", "answer": "  still in love with?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 115, "asentId": 116}, {"question": " yeah!", "answer": " i\u0092m not in love with ross!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 117, "asentId": 118}, {"question": " oh. no. no. good! yeah, me neither.", "answer": " phoebe, i\u0092m going to ross\u0092s wedding because he is my ex-boyfriend and that would be really uncomfortable. not because, i\u0092m still in love with him! i mean, hey, y\u0092know, i like ross as much as the next guy, y\u0092know? clearly i have feelings for him, but feelings don\u0092t mean love! i mean, i still have loving feelings for ross. yeah! but, i have, i have continuing feelings of love, but that doesn\u0092t mean that-that i\u0092m still in love with him. y\u0092know? i-i have sexual feelings for him, but i do love him\u0097ohh! oh my god! oh my\u0097why didn\u0092t you tell me?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 119, "asentId": 120}, {"question": " we thought you knew!", "answer": " we?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 121, "asentId": 122}, {"question": " yeah, we all know! we talk about it all the time!", "answer": " you all know? does ross know?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 123, "asentId": 124}, {"question": " oh no, ross doesn\u0092t know anything.", "answer": " oh, i can not believe you didn\u0092t tell me!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 125, "asentId": 126}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " so, what are you guys in the market for? we\u0092ve got uh, scarves, tulip post cards...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 129, "asentId": 130}, {"question": " check this out? huh?  yeah. that\u0092s the stuff. what do you think?", "answer": " well, i don\u0092t have to buy that, \"i\u0092m with stupid\" t-shirt anymore.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 131, "asentId": 132}, {"question": " all right, look, you\u0092re not really gonna buy that are you? don\u0092t you think you\u0092ve embarrassed me enough for one day?", "answer": " oh, i embarrass you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 135, "asentId": 136}, {"question": " how can i answer that when i\u0092m pretending i don\u0092t know you?", "answer": " he\u0092s just jealous. you\u0092ll fit right in; all londoners wear them!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 137, "asentId": 138}, {"question": " oh really? then how come no one here is wearing them?", "answer": "  they\u0092re all tourists.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 139, "asentId": 140}, {"question": " all right, look, if you insist on wearing that, in public, y\u0092know, you\u0092re gonna spend the rest of the afternoon all by yourself.", "answer": " oh yeah?  if you\u0092re gonna make me choose between you and the hat? i choose the hat.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 141, "asentId": 142}, {"question": " good choice.", "answer": " thanks.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 143, "asentId": 144}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": " hey! i just spoke to your dad, and you know what? he seems to think we\u0092ll be able to find a new place for the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 147, "asentId": 148}, {"question": " we don\u0092t have to.", "answer": " whoa-whoa-what? you found a place?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 149, "asentId": 150}, {"question": " no. but, monica and i were talking, and-and i was so upset about the hall being knocked down, and she suggested that we put the wedding off for a bit.", "answer": " she said what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 151, "asentId": 152}, {"question": " she said, \"if i\u0092m not gonna be happy getting married somewhere that we find in a day, well then we should just postpone it.\"", "answer": " postpone it? emily, do you think monica realises how much our parents spent on this wedding? do you my sister\u0092s teeny-tiny little brain comprehends that people took time out of their lives to fly thousands of miles to be here, huh?  this isn\u0092t right.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 153, "asentId": 154}, {"question": " i realize that people are going to be disappointed. but, i\u0092m sure they\u0092ll come back when we can do it right.", "answer": " i can\u0092t ask people to do that? would you ask people to do that?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 155, "asentId": 156}, {"question": " don\u0092t you point your pants at me!  we have no choice! anywhere that\u0092s half-decent would\u0092ve be booked months ago, ross don\u0092t you understand? this is our wedding i\u0092m talking about.", "answer": " the only thing i understand is; postponing it is not an option. this is when we\u0092re getting married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 157, "asentId": 158}, {"question": " so what are you saying? it\u0092s now or never?", "answer": " no. i\u0092m saying it\u0092s now.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 159, "asentId": 160}, {"question": " or?", "answer": " there\u0092s no \u0091or\u0092 in mind. what is wrong with these pants?!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 161, "asentId": 162}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": "  hi.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 167, "asentId": 168}, {"question": " so, did shopping make you feel any better about ross?", "answer": " manhattan does not have enough stores.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 169, "asentId": 170}, {"question": " well, i think i can help you get over him.", "answer": " you can?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 171, "asentId": 172}, {"question": " yeah. i just need you to bring me some photos of ross.", "answer": " um-hmm.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 173, "asentId": 174}, {"question": " and a small piece of chocolate.", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 175, "asentId": 176}, {"question": " ooh, is this one of those things where you throw it in a bag with some graveyard dirt and hang it from a north-facing tree?", "answer": " uh, only if you have the hiccups too. yeah, the pictures are for you, the water and the chocolate is for me. i just didn\u0092t feel like getting up. okay, i\u0092m gonna show you a picture of ross. okay? and you\u0092re going to remember all of the bad things about him. all right? really focus on his flaws.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 179, "asentId": 180}, {"question": " i can do that. i certainly did it when we were going out.", "answer": " okay. umm, before we get started, i just wanna say for the record that i love ross, i think he\u0092s such a great guy. here.  okay, now, close your eyes. and imagine that you\u0092re with ross okay and imagine that you\u0092re kissing him. and you\u0092re-you\u0092re running your hands all over his body. and then you run your hands through his hair, but eew-oh gross it\u0092s some kind of grease, it\u0092s\u0097uck! hah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 181, "asentId": 182}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, his uh, his hair never really bothered me that much, and y\u0092know it was always more crunchy than it was greasy.", "answer": " okay, this is going to be harder than i thought. umm, let\u0092s try some uh, aversion therapy.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 183, "asentId": 184}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 185, "asentId": 186}, {"question": " all right.", "answer": " so uh, now look at the picture\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 187, "asentId": 188}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " all right, and umm\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 189, "asentId": 190}, {"question": " ow!", "answer": " okay, how do you feel now?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 191, "asentId": 192}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 195, "asentId": 196}, {"question": " oh.  sorry!", "answer": " no-no-no, y\u0092know what? i really shouldn\u0092t have said that you were embarrassing me, i mean that really wasn\u0092t cool. and if it makes you feel any better, i\u0092ve had a really lousy day.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 197, "asentId": 198}, {"question": " me too.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 199, "asentId": 200}, {"question": " noo!! i\u0092ve had the best day ever! dude, check this out!", "answer": "  hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 201, "asentId": 202}, {"question": "  okay, so say hi to my friend and tell him that you like the hat.", "answer": "  okay, so umm, what\u0092s your friend\u0092s name?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 205, "asentId": 206}, {"question": "  oh, chandler.", "answer": " hi chandler!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 207, "asentId": 208}, {"question": " that\u0092s\u009a that\u0092s was\u009a", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 209, "asentId": 210}, {"question": " that\u0092s fergie baby!!", "answer": " joey says you don\u0092t really like his hat, but i think it\u0092s kinda dashing.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 211, "asentId": 212}, {"question": " how did you? how? how?", "answer": " well, i was trying to figure out how to get to buckingham palace, right? so, i\u0092m in my map and-and\u009a hey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 213, "asentId": 214}, {"question": " hey!", "answer": " hi. i understand you had a little talk with emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 215, "asentId": 216}, {"question": "  yes, i did! and you are welcome!", "answer": " am i?! and was it your idea to postpone the wedding?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 217, "asentId": 218}, {"question": " umm\u009a", "answer": " i\u0092m gonna go to the bathroom.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 219, "asentId": 220}, {"question": " hey-hey, since you\u0092re the \u0091fix-it\u0092 lady, here\u0092s a pickle, what do you do when the bride says she doesn\u0092t want to have the wedding at all?", "answer": " she said that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 223, "asentId": 224}, {"question": " yeah.", "answer": " why?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 225, "asentId": 226}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know, i told her it was stupid to put off the wedding just because the hall was gone and she liked flipped out.", "answer": " oh my god. you\u0092re even dumber than i am!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 227, "asentId": 228}, {"question": " excuse me?", "answer": " ross, how long have you been planning this wedding?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 229, "asentId": 230}, {"question": " i don\u0092t know. a month?", "answer": " emily has probably been planning it since she was five! ever since the first time she took a pillowcase and hung it off the back of her head. that\u0092s what we did! we dreamed about the perfect wedding, and the perfect place, with the perfect four-tiered wedding cake , with the little people on top.  thanks. but the most important part is that we had the perfect guy who understood just how important all that other stuff was.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 231, "asentId": 232}, {"question": " i had no idea. and that-that pillowcase thing, i thought you guys were just doing the flying nun.", "answer": " sometimes we were.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 233, "asentId": 234}, {"question": " come on. you gotta help me figure out what to do. okay?", "answer": " okay.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 235, "asentId": 236}, {"question": " that was pretty intense huh?", "answer": " yeah.  hey, i hope ross didn\u0092t think that we just went in there because we were uncomfortable being out here!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 239, "asentId": 240}, {"question": " hello.", "answer": "  hey, pheebs! it\u0092s joey!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 243, "asentId": 244}, {"question": " hey, joey! hey! ooh! ooh! i just say someone on the\u0097that looks just like you on the subway. and i was gonna go over and say \u0091hi!\u0092 but then i figured, he doesn\u0092t care if he looks like you.", "answer": " that just cost me four bucks. but uh listen, i just called to see how the chick and the duck are doing?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 245, "asentId": 246}, {"question": " ohh, they\u0092re having a great time with their aunt phoebe! aunt rachel hasn\u0092t been helpful at all. so, do you miss me?", "answer": " kinda, but i\u0092ve just been having way too much fun.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 247, "asentId": 248}, {"question": " so you\u0092re not homesick yet?", "answer": " no, i don\u0092t think so.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 249, "asentId": 250}, {"question": " all right, the seven of us miss you.", "answer": " who\u0092s seven?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 251, "asentId": 252}, {"question": " y\u0092know, me, rachel, the birds, the babies\u009a", "answer": " ahh, the babies miss me?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 253, "asentId": 254}, {"question": " ooh, the pizza guy\u0092s here!", "answer": " what? you ordered pizza without me?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 255, "asentId": 256}, {"question": " yeah. but y\u0092know we were thinking about you, y\u0092know we ordered the joey special.", "answer": " two pizzas?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 257, "asentId": 258}, {"question": " yep! okay, gotta go, talk to you later.", "answer": " wait, well, where did you get it from?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 259, "asentId": 260}, {"question": " monica, why have you brought me here of all places?!", "answer": " you\u0092ll see.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 261, "asentId": 262}, {"question": " oh god.", "answer": " okay? but-but imagine a lot more lights, okay? and-and y\u0092know fewer bricks, and-and-and flowers, and candles\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 265, "asentId": 266}, {"question": " and the musicians, look, they can go over here , okay? and the chairs can face this way , and\u009a  you", "answer": " but-but, if you don\u0092t love this, we\u0092ll do it in any other place at any other time. really, it\u0092s fine, whatever you want.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 267, "asentId": 268}, {"question": " it\u0092s perfect.", "answer": " and, i don\u0092t know, if it starts to rain\u009a", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 269, "asentId": 270}, {"question": " pheebs?", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 275, "asentId": 276}, {"question": " do you remember where the duck food is?", "answer": " yeah, it\u0092s in the guys\u0092 apartment under the sink. why?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 277, "asentId": 278}, {"question": "  because i\u0092m going to london.", "answer": " what?! what do you mean you\u0092re going to london?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 279, "asentId": 280}, {"question": " i\u0097rachel, you can\u0092t go! ross loves emily!", "answer": " yeah, i know, i know, i know he does. but i have to tell him how i feel! he deserves to have all the information and then he can make an informed decision.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 283, "asentId": 284}, {"question": " that\u0092s not why you\u0092re going! you\u0092re going because you hope he\u0092s gonna say, \"yeah, i love you too, rach. forget that british chippy.\"", "answer": " ohh\u0097do you think he will?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 285, "asentId": 286}, {"question": " no! because he\u0092s in love with the british chippy! look, rachel, if you go, you\u0092re just gonna mess with his head and ruin his wedding! y\u0092know, it\u0092s too late! you missed you\u0092re chance! i\u0092m sorry, i know this must be really hard, it\u0092s over.", "answer": " y\u0092know what? no. it\u0092s not over until someone says, \"i do.\"", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 287, "asentId": 288}, {"question": " the waltham residence.", "answer": " oh...yes..is this..umm..emily\u0092s parents\u0092 house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 291, "asentId": 292}, {"question": " this is the housekeeper speaking. and by the way, young lady, that is not how one addresses oneself on the telephone. first one identifies oneself and then asks for the person with whom one wishes to speak.", "answer": "  this is phoebe buffay. i was wondering, please, if-if it\u0092s not too much trouble, please, umm, might i speak to miss emily waltham, please?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 293, "asentId": 294}, {"question": " miss waltham, is at the rehearsal dinner and it\u0092s not polite to make fun of people. goodbye.", "answer": " no no no, i\u0092ll be nice, i swear!!! \u00a0 could you just give me the number for where they are?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 295, "asentId": 296}, {"question": " i\u0092m afraid, i\u0092m not at liberty to divulge that information.", "answer": " ok, somebody is on their way to ruin wedding okay. and i have to warn somebody, alright. so if you don\u0092t give me that number then i\u0092m going to come over there and kick your snooty ass all the way to new glocken..shire.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 297, "asentId": 298}, {"question": " hangs up.", "answer": " hello, hello. ohh, ohh, she knew i could kick her ass.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 299, "asentId": 300}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hi. mom. dad.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 301, "asentId": 302}, {"question": " sweetheart. oh sorry were late, my fault, i insisted on riding the tube.", "answer": "  judy, the kids..", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 303, "asentId": 304}, {"question": " jack, that\u0092s what they call the subway.", "answer": " ohh, i thought that you.... ross and monica: dad, dad. we got it!! we got it!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 305, "asentId": 306}, {"question": " ohh, here comes my dad and stepmum. mister and misses geller, this is steven and andrea waltham.", "answer": "  hello. hello. how do you do? how do you do? very nice to meet you.  darling it\u0092s the gellers.   darling, it\u0092s the gellers.  she\u0092s very self-absorbed, you know. i should never have married her.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 307, "asentId": 308}, {"question": "  sorry, what?", "answer": " it\u0092s the gellers!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 309, "asentId": 310}, {"question": " where?", "answer": " well there\u0092s one  and there\u0092s another .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 311, "asentId": 312}, {"question": " lovely to meet you.", "answer": " terribly nice of you to offer to pay for half the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 313, "asentId": 314}, {"question": " ohh forget it. too hell with tradition, we\u0092re happy to do it.", "answer": " we know how expensive weddings can be, besides this may be the only wedding we get to throw .", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 315, "asentId": 316}, {"question": " what\u0092s in it?", "answer": " goat cheese, water chestnuts, and panchetta.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 321, "asentId": 322}, {"question": " that\u0092s not food...no, i don\u0092t, no... everything's different here...i want to go home. i...i miss my family. i miss the coffee house. i can\u0092t even remember what phoebe looks like.", "answer": " joey, it\u0092s been three days, okay.. your just a little homesick, okay. would you just try to relax. just, just try to enjoy yourself.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 323, "asentId": 324}, {"question": "  what the hell!!!", "answer": " what\u0092s up, dad?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 327, "asentId": 328}, {"question": " this bill for my half of the wedding. it\u0092s insane.", "answer": " how could it be so much? the receptions at their house.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 329, "asentId": 330}, {"question": "  flowers, liquor, recarpet first floor. new guest bath, landscaping. i\u0092m paying to remodel this guys house.  i\u0092m going to give that son on a bitch, a piece of my mind.", "answer": " dad, dad, please. look i don\u0092t want anything to upset emily tonight. alright, she's had a hard enough couple of days as it is.  now here, here, let me go talk to him, okay?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 331, "asentId": 332}, {"question": " and you tell him no one takes advantage of the gellers.", "answer": " ooh, jack.... sometimes i forget how powerful you can be.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 333, "asentId": 334}, {"question": "  ooh, ooh, ooh,ooh,ooh.  hi.", "answer": "  hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 337, "asentId": 338}, {"question": "  hello. umm, when is your next flight to london?", "answer": "  there\u0092s one leaving in thirty minutes.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 339, "asentId": 340}, {"question": " ohh, good.", "answer": " and i do have one seat left.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 341, "asentId": 342}, {"question": " ohh, thank you, thank you, thank you.", "answer": " the last minute fare on this ticket is twenty seven hundred dollars.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 343, "asentId": 344}, {"question": "  ohh, i just don\u0092t think i have enough left on my credit card.", "answer": " well you can split it with another credit card.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 345, "asentId": 346}, {"question": " ohh, okay, how about five.  ohh, thank you.", "answer": " i\u0092m just going to need to see your passport.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 347, "asentId": 348}, {"question": " look, face it, my father is not going to pay for the build-in barbecue and believe me you can kiss you gazebo goodbye. now i might be able to get you the new lawn.", "answer": " ahh, then you have to give us the lawn ornaments.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 353, "asentId": 354}, {"question": " i go back there with lawn ornaments, he\u0092s going to laugh in my face.", "answer": " this is ridiculous. i mean we had an agreement.  will you say something, steven?! please!!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 355, "asentId": 356}, {"question": "  hi, pheebs.", "answer": "  oh thank god. oh, you changed your mind. oh, look i know you probably want to be alone, and you don\u0092t want to talk about it, that\u0092s fine. i just want you to know, i think you are doing the right thing and...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 359, "asentId": 360}, {"question": "  bye, pheebs.", "answer": "  wait!! where are you going?! what are you doing?! no!! wait!!  god!! why am i always pregnant when she does that?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 361, "asentId": 362}, {"question": " hello, waltham interiors.", "answer": " oh, hi, mrs. waltham. i need to speak with ether one of the best men, or ross\u0092s sister monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 365, "asentId": 366}, {"question": " who is this?", "answer": " oh, i\u0092m phoebe buffay. i\u0092m one of ross\u0092s best friends.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 367, "asentId": 368}, {"question": " well, if you\u0092re on e of ross\u0092s best friends, why aren\u0092t you here?", "answer": " yeah, um, i can\u0092t fly. i\u0092m having my brother\u0092s babies.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 369, "asentId": 370}, {"question": " oh, am i on the radio?", "answer": " no..umm, could i talk to one of them? it\u0092s very very important.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 371, "asentId": 372}, {"question": " ohh! okay, i\u0092m going to have to kick her ass too.", "answer": "  and i\u0092m sure we\u0092re all very excited that ross and emily are getting married at montgomery hall. i mean to think, my friend getting married in monty hall.  ohh, come on!! monty hall!! lets make a deal!! come on, you people!! all right, forget it!! congratulations, ross and emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 375, "asentId": 376}, {"question": "  are you going home? i was hoping to get to know you better.", "answer": "  i\u0092m not going anywhere, sweetheart.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 379, "asentId": 380}, {"question": " out loud?", "answer": " well i didn\u0092t want everyone to think i was stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 383, "asentId": 384}, {"question": " so how are you doing?", "answer": " my mother\u0092s driving me crazy, but ross is getting married. i\u0092m happy.  i\u0092m not going to let anything spoil that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 385, "asentId": 386}, {"question": " i just want to say that ross is a wonderful young man.", "answer": " well, thanks, we like him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 387, "asentId": 388}, {"question": " there\u0092s no way in hell, i\u0092m paying for it.", "answer": " look, were down to just one point. could we please, maybe just settle it after the wedding.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 391, "asentId": 392}, {"question": " the guy was hammered, okay? there\u0092s no way, you look like ross\u0092s mother.", "answer": " then why would he say it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 395, "asentId": 396}, {"question": " because he\u0092s crazy. okay? he came up to me earlier and thanked me for my very moving performance in titanic.", "answer": " oh, my mother\u0092s right. i\u0092m never going to get married.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 397, "asentId": 398}, {"question": " ahh, you know what? that is....who wouldn\u0092t want you?", "answer": " ohh, please?! i\u0092m a single mom, with a thirty year old son!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 399, "asentId": 400}, {"question": " hi, i\u0092m back. listen, i need to...", "answer": " hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 401, "asentId": 402}, {"question": " hello. i need to get on the 11 o'clock flight.", "answer": " oh i\u0092m afraid that plane has already pulled away from the gate.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 403, "asentId": 404}, {"question": " okay, you know what/ you\u0092re going to have to call that plane and tell them to swing around and come and pick me up.", "answer": " i can\u0092t do that.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 405, "asentId": 406}, {"question": " sure, you know what? come on, we\u0092ll just tell them that there was like a problem with like the \"engine\".", "answer": " i\u0092m afraid i\u0092m going to have to ask you to step aside, miss.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 407, "asentId": 408}, {"question": " look, if i don\u0092t get to london!! he is going to marry that other girl!!!", "answer": " i can\u0092t imagine why.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 409, "asentId": 410}, {"question": "  i\u0092m getting married today!! whoo-hoo!!", "answer": "  morning, ross.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 413, "asentId": 414}, {"question": " i\u0092m getting married, to..day!!", "answer": " yeah you are!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 415, "asentId": 416}, {"question": " ahh, whoo-hoo!!(he runs back out the door.", "answer": "  do you think he knew i was here?  commercial break", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 417, "asentId": 418}, {"question": " well i\u0092ve-i\u0092ve never done that with you before.", "answer": "  nope.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 419, "asentId": 420}, {"question": " so, ahh, how are ya? how ya...how ya... you okay?", "answer": " yep, yep...you?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 421, "asentId": 422}, {"question": " yes...yes..uh-huh, you? we did you.", "answer": " well...i\u0092d better get going.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 423, "asentId": 424}, {"question": " oh yea yea, absolutely.", "answer": "  could you not look?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 425, "asentId": 426}, {"question": " ahh, ahh, excuse me.", "answer": " yeah?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 431, "asentId": 432}, {"question": " if you\u0092re planning on doing that throughout the entire flight. please tell me now. so that i could that a sedative...or perhaps slip you one.", "answer": " oh. i\u0092m sorry. i\u0092m very sorry. sorry.  it\u0092s just, i\u0092m ahh, i\u0092m kinda excited. i\u0092m, ahh, going to london to ahh, tell this guy that i love him and...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 433, "asentId": 434}, {"question": " hello?", "answer": "  hey, were the hell have you been?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 435, "asentId": 436}, {"question": " hey. i spent the night out. i met this cute bridesmaid. she is so...", "answer": " i don\u0092t want to hear about her!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 437, "asentId": 438}, {"question": " ahh pheebs, you know you\u0092re still my number one girl.", "answer": " no! no, we have an emergency. okay? rachel\u0092s coming to london.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 439, "asentId": 440}, {"question": " ohh great!!!", "answer": " no it\u0092s not great. no, she\u0092s coming to tell ross that she loves him.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 441, "asentId": 442}, {"question": "  but, he loves emily?", "answer": " i know that!!! you have to stop her!! she\u0092s going to ruin the wedding!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 443, "asentId": 444}, {"question": " okay.", "answer": " all right, so, okay...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 445, "asentId": 446}, {"question": " hold on. hold on.  rachel coming. do...something.", "answer": " okay, so i\u0092m done my part, okay. it\u0092s your responsibility now, okay. the burden is off me, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 447, "asentId": 448}, {"question": " right!", "answer": " so tell me about this girl?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 449, "asentId": 450}, {"question": " hey.", "answer": " hey.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 451, "asentId": 452}, {"question": " have you seen monica?", "answer": "  i\u0092m not seeing monica.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 453, "asentId": 454}, {"question": "  what?", "answer": " what?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 455, "asentId": 456}, {"question": " look we\u0092ve got to find her. phoebe just called!! rachel\u0092s coming to tell ross she loves him!!", "answer": " oh my god!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 457, "asentId": 458}, {"question": " i know! that\u0092s why we got to find monica!! you know where she is?", "answer": " no!! okay!! what\u0092s with the third degree?! why don\u0092t you just shine a light in my eyes?!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 459, "asentId": 460}, {"question": " ...and so then i realized. all this stuff i had been doing. proposing to joshua, lying to ross about why i couldn\u0092t come to the wedding. was all just a way of...", "answer": "  oh, oh oh!! i\u0092m sorry, can i interrupt? you know i just want to say..that you are a horrible, horrible person.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 461, "asentId": 462}, {"question": " ehh, pardon me?", "answer": " you say you love this man, yet you\u0092re about to ruin the happiest day of his life. i\u0092m afraid i have to agree with you friend pheebs.. this is a..this is a...terrible, terrible plan.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 463, "asentId": 464}, {"question": " but he has to know how i feel!", "answer": " but why? he loves this...this emily person. no good can come of this.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 465, "asentId": 466}, {"question": "  well i-i think your wrong.", "answer": " oh-no.and by the way, it seems to be perfectly clear that you were on a break.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 467, "asentId": 468}, {"question": "  oh my god! it\u0092s like a fairyland.", "answer": " i know, it\u0092s horrible isn\u0092t it?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 469, "asentId": 470}, {"question": " well, i love it. i only hope my wedding looks this good.", "answer": " i just hope...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 471, "asentId": 472}, {"question": "  pisst, monica. alright, we really need to start looking out for rachel. i\u0092ll cover the front door. you watch that big hole at the back of the building and i got chandler covering ross.", "answer": "  why would i care where chandler is? you know uhh...you know sometimes i don\u0092t even like chandler.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 475, "asentId": 476}, {"question": "  i do. i do. i do.", "answer": " oh yea, your right. it\u0092s the second one.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 479, "asentId": 480}, {"question": " really?", "answer": " joey\u0092s in the front entrance watching for rachel. the bridesmaid he met at the rehearsal dinner come in.)", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 481, "asentId": 482}, {"question": " hello joey.", "answer": " hey, felicity.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 483, "asentId": 484}, {"question": " umm, i thought about you all day.", "answer": " yeah.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 485, "asentId": 486}, {"question": " um-hum. talk new york to me again.", "answer": "  fuggetaboutit.  how you doin?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 487, "asentId": 488}, {"question": " there\u0092s nothing to discuss. we\u0092re not paying for your wine cellar.", "answer": "  you-you have to meet me in the middle here.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 493, "asentId": 494}, {"question": "  hey, you keep pushing me on this, my foots going to meet the middle of your ass.", "answer": " dad!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 495, "asentId": 496}, {"question": " what-what\u0092s going on?!", "answer": " nothing, nothing. everything's under control.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 497, "asentId": 498}, {"question": " you want a piece of me, sir? is that what your saying?  you want a piece of me?", "answer": " okay! okay! that\u0092s it!! parents!! parents!! back away!! all right, this is our wedding day! >from now on everyone gets along, and if i hear one more word. no grandchildren!  that\u0092s right!!", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 499, "asentId": 500}, {"question": " okay, okay.", "answer": " sorry old boy, sorry. sorry. sorry.  i could kill you with my thumb, you know.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 501, "asentId": 502}, {"question": " what was all that about?", "answer": "  it was...this disagreement over... my god. you...you look beautiful.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 503, "asentId": 504}, {"question": "  ohh... oh! you were not meant to see me before the wedding. it\u0092s bad luck.", "answer": " you know what, i think we\u0092ve had all the bad luck we\u0092re going to have.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 505, "asentId": 506}, {"question": " my god. rachel!  your here. i can\u0092t believe it.  what happen? why are you here?", "answer": " well i just came... i just needed to tell you... congratulations.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 507, "asentId": 508}, {"question": "  hello, waltham interiors.", "answer": " mrs. waltham. hi. it\u0092s phoebe again.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 509, "asentId": 510}, {"question": "  why?!", "answer": " yea. can i please, please, please talk to one of the best men? this is going to be the last time i promise.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 511, "asentId": 512}, {"question": "  joey there\u0092s a girl on the phone for you.", "answer": "  ohh great!!  hello.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 513, "asentId": 514}, {"question": " did you stop rachel?", "answer": " no, but it\u0092s okay. she just came in and gave him a hug, that it.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 515, "asentId": 516}, {"question": " so nothing got ruined?", "answer": " no.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 517, "asentId": 518}, {"question": " oh that\u0092s so great! ohh, so what\u0092s going on now?", "answer": " ah, i\u0092m-i\u0092m walking down the aisle...still walking.  i\u0092m about to pass the bridesmaid i hooked up with last night.  hey!  i told her \"hey.\" and now i\u0092m at the front with ross. it\u0092s phoebe.  he looks pretty mad. uh...i\u0092d better go.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 519, "asentId": 520}, {"question": " what we did last night was....", "answer": " stupid.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 523, "asentId": 524}, {"question": " what were we thinking?", "answer": " i\u0092m coming over tonight though, right?", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 527, "asentId": 528}, {"question": " friends. family. we are gathered to celebrate here today the joyous union of ross and emily. may the happiness we share with them today be with them always. now emily, repeat after me. i, emily...", "answer": " i, emily...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 531, "asentId": 532}, {"question": " take thee ross...", "answer": " take thee ross...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 533, "asentId": 534}, {"question": " as my lawfully wedded husband, in sickness and in health, till death parts us.", "answer": " as my lawfully wedded husband, in sickness and in health, until death parts us.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 535, "asentId": 536}, {"question": " now ross, repeat after me. i ross...", "answer": " i ross...", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 537, "asentId": 538}, {"question": " take thee, emily...", "answer": " take thee, rachel... emily.  emily.", "docId": "friendsCopy/s4/ep23.txt.cleaned", "qsentId": 539, "asentId": 540}]